chickensoup.com 2019-06-10

# Privacy Policy | Chicken Soup for the Soul

**Last Updated: March 27, 2019**

We respect your privacy, and we want you to know how we use the information you provide to us. This is the Privacy Policy (the “Privacy Policy”) of Chicken Soup for the Soul LLC and its subsidiary companies or any of its wholly or partially owned subsidiaries (“CSS,” “us” or “we”), which applies to the websites located at [www.chickensoup.com](https://www.chickensoup.com/), [chickensouppets.com](https://chickensouppets.com/), [aplus.com](https://aplus.com/), [www.popcornflix.com](https://www.popcornflix.com/), [cssentertainment.com](https://cssentertainment.com/), [www.screenmedia.net](http://www.screenmedia.net/ "www.screenmedia.net"), and [www.truli.com](http://www.truli.com/ "www.truli.com"), affiliate sites, subdomains (collectively, the “Sites”), mobile versions (the “Applications”) and blogs (collectively our “Services”), unless a different policy is provided on a particular Site or Application. In this Privacy Policy, we describe the information we collect, how CSS uses and discloses the information, and your choices regarding our information collection practices.

Please read this Privacy Policy carefully. By visiting our Sites, our Applications and using our Services, you agree that your information, including your personal information, will be handled as described in this Privacy Policy, which is incorporated by reference into this [Terms of Use](https://www.chickensoup.com/terms-of-use).

## Introduction

This Privacy Policy explains the following:

  * Information We Collect;
  * Use of Cookies, Flash Cookies, HTML5, Web Beacons, and Other Tracking Devices;
  * Security of Information;
  * Use of Your Information;
  * Sharing Information;
  * How Long We Will Hold Information;
  * User Generated Content;
  * Advertising;
  * Our Commitment to Children’s Privacy;
  * Personal Information Review and Revision Policies;
  * Unsubscribe and Data Removal Policies;
  * Your California Privacy Rights;
  * Other Sites and Services;
  * Consent to Processing in the United States;
  * Revisions to Privacy Policy;
  * Choice of Law; and
  * Questions about our Privacy Policy and How To Contact Us.

## Information We Collect

We collect information from and about you, including personal information and information about your use of the Sites, the Applications, and our Services. Specifically, we collect information: (1) directly from you, such as when you register to use our Sites, request our email newsletters, send submissions or participate in polls, surveys, contests, sweepstakes, or other offers; (2) from third parties, such as when you log in through a social networking (3) automatically, as you move through our Sites and our Applications, such as Sites’ usage, browser types, IP addresses or device IDs, and other data, as discussed below.

_**Information We Collect Directly From You.**_ We request information from you when you register for an account for our Sites request our newsletters, participate in our polls, surveys, contests, sweepstakes, story submissions, and other promotions, and when you contact us regarding questions or concerns you may have with the Sites or our Services. Depending upon the particular activity, we may request the following information from you: your name, username, email address, zip code, phone number, gender, age range, income range, username, and, for members of [www.chickensoup.com](http://www.chickensoup.com/ "www.chickensoup.com"), credit card and billing information. Some information is optional. You are under no obligation to provide any information. However, if you should choose to withhold requested information, we may not be able to provide you with certain services.

  * _Submissions for Chicken Soup for the Soul Books._ If you send us an original story or poem submission to be considered for publication in a Chicken Soup for the Soul book, we ask you for information such as:
    * Contact information such as name, email address, mailing address, phone and fax numbers.
    * The title and complete text of your submission.
    * If your submission is accepted, we request further information in order to ensure we can complete the publication of your work.

_**Information We Collect About You From Third Parties.**_

  * _Social Networking Sites._ You may log onto our Sites through social networking applications, such as Facebook and Twitter. From time to time, we may add the capability to log into our Sites through different social networking sites. If you log into our Services through a social networking site, we will request your name and certain basic information. We also may request certain permissions from you, which vary based on the social networking site. For information about how the particular social networking site may disclose your information, including any information you make public, please consult their privacy policy. We have no control over how a third party social networking site uses or discloses the personal information that you provide to it. We store the information that we receive from the social networking site along with other information that we collect from you or receive about you.

_**Information We Collect Automatically.**_ We use cookies, web beacons, Flash, and other automated devices to collect information about you when you visit our Sites and our Applications. Specifically, we collect the following information about your use of our Sites via these technologies: your browser type and operating system; web pages you view; links you click; your IP address; your interaction with the Sites; length of time you are logged in to our Sites; and websites visited before our Sites. With regard to the Applications, we may collect your mobile device ID; location and language information; device name and model; operating system type, IP address, name and version; your activities within the Applications; and the length of time that you are logged into our Applications. We will request your information before we collect your location. Please see the section “Use of Cookies, Flash Cookies, HTML5, Web Beacons, and Other Tracking Devices” below for more information about our use of these tracking devices. We may use the information gathered through these methods in anonymous or aggregated form to analyze ways to improve our Services. This information may be associated with your username and may be combined with other information, including personal information that we collect about you.

_**Location Information.**_ If you are using our Applications, we also may collect your location. We will request your permission prior to doing so. We may combine your location information with other information that we have collected about you.

## Use of Cookies, Flash Cookies, HTML5, Web Beacons, and Other Tracking Devices

When you interact with our Services, we strive to make your experience easy and meaningful. We or our third party service providers use cookies, web beacons (including clear GIFs), Flash LSOs, and similar technologies to track user activity and collect data about our Sites, Services, and our users. As stated above, we may combine this data with the personal information we have collected from or about you.

_**Cookies.**_ We use browser “cookies” on our Sites. Cookies are a website’s way of remembering who you are. A cookie is a small text file that is stored on your computer’s hard drive or stored temporarily in your computer’s memory. There are two kinds of cookies, and we use both types of cookies on our Sites: “session” cookies and “persistent” cookies. Session cookies are deleted when you close your browser. Persistent cookies remain on your computer and retain information for later use tomorrow, next month or whenever they are set to expire. We use cookies to help us to identify account holders and to optimize their experience on our Sites. Also, we will use cookies to monitor and maintain information about your use of this Sites.

Most Web browsers accept cookies automatically. You can delete cookies manually or set your browser to automatically delete cookies on a pre-determined schedule. If you decline to accept cookies, you may not be able to take advantage of or participate in certain features of our Sites.

Other companies that place advertising on our Sites also have the ability to assign their cookies to you. You can opt out of the collection of certain information about you by many online advertisers. Please see the section below entitled “Advertising” for additional information.

_**Use of Flash Cookies and HTML5.**_ Our Services enable the use of the Adobe Flash Player. Your use of the Adobe Flash Player generates “flash cookies” (also known as “persistent identification elements” or “local shared objects”). The Adobe Flash Player (and similar applications) uses flash cookies to remember user settings, preferences and usage in a manner similar to the browser cookies referenced above. Flash cookies can store more information than browser cookies and are managed through a different interface than the one provided by your Web browser. You can control the degree to which you accept flash cookies by accessing your Adobe Flash Player management tools directly through the settings manager for Adobe Flash, located at [http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/sett...](http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager.html "http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager.html"). (Users running the Windows operating system can generally view flash cookie files in this folder: \Documents and Settings\\[username]\Application Data\Macromedia\Flash Player. Users running the Apple operating system can generally view flash cookie files in this folder: /users/[username]/Library/Preferences/macromedia/Flash Player. Flash cookies, or LSO files are stored typically with an “.SOL” extension. If you do not allow flash cookies on your computer, you may not be able to take advantage of or participate in certain features of our Services.

HTML is the software language used for building most of the sites on the internet. Some HTML5 code may allow your responses to advertising and other activities to be monitored across websites, and for such information to be stored on your computer or mobile device and accessed by others you do or have done business with. CSS accesses user activity information stored through this feature of HTML5. As with cookies, other companies that place advertising on our Site may have the ability to access information using this feature of HTML5. CSS does not control and is not responsible for any such access or for their use of information obtained.

_**Web Beacons.**_ Our Web pages or e-mail messages may contain a small graphic image called a Web beacon, which is sometimes also called a “clear gif,” that allows us to monitor and collect certain information about our users, such as the type of browser requesting the Web beacon, the IP address of the computer that the Web beacon is sent to and the time the Web beacon was viewed. Web beacons can be very small or invisible to the user, but, in general, any electronic image viewed as part of a Web page or email, including HTML-based content, can act as a Web beacon. We may use Web beacons to count visitors to our Web pages or to monitor how our users navigate our Sites, and we may include Web beacons in email messages in order to count how many of the messages we sent were actually opened or acted upon. We use Web beacons to compile aggregate statistics about our Sites and our marketing campaigns.

_**Analytics.**_ Each time a visitor comes to the Sites or uses our Applications, our servers collect information, including, for example, the visitor’s domain name (e.g., the website that you came from), referral data (e.g., depending on your browser, the address of the last page or series of pages you visited prior to clicking through to our Sites), and browser and platform type. We also count, track and aggregate each visitor’s activity as part of our analysis of general traffic flows at our Sites and on our Applications (e.g., tracking where traffic comes from, how traffic flows within the Sites and our Applications, etc.). We collect some of this data directly, and we also engage third party service providers (e.g., Google Analytics) who use the technologies described in this section, to collect this information and to assist us with our analytics.

More information on how Google uses data when you use our Site or Applications: <http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/>

_**reCAPTCHA.**_ Some of our Sites use reCAPTCHA, a free service from Google, to help prevent automated spammers from accessing our Sites. For example, you may see reCAPTCHA when you register for a new account, request to reset your password, or submit a contact form message. In order to determine whether a user is a human or a spam robot, the reCAPTCHA service collects hardware and software information, such as device and application data, which is then sent to Google for analysis. reCAPTCHA also creates and sets cookies. As stated by the reCAPTCHA API Terms of Service, the information collected in connection with use of the reCAPTCHA service will be used for improving reCAPTCHA and for general security purposes, and information collected for reCAPTCHA will not be used for personalized advertising by Google. By using our Sites, you acknowledge and agree that your information used by reCAPTCHA will also be subject to the Google Privacy Policy at <https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/>

_**Google Maps.**_ We use Google Maps to provide mapping and location features on our Sites, such as our store locator that allows you to find retailers that carry our pet food products. To provide these services, Google collects data from us and you, such as IP addresses, latitude/longitude coordinates, zip code, city, state, country, or other search terms, as well as cookies and personal data such as device identifiers. By using Google Maps, you acknowledge and agree to the Google Maps/Google Earth Additional Terms of Service at <https://maps.google.com/help/terms_maps.html> and the Google Privacy Policy at <https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/>

## Security of Information

CSS makes efforts to protect your information. However, no website, Internet transmission, computer system or wireless connection is completely secure. CSS cannot guarantee that unauthorized access or disclosure, hacking, data loss or other breaches will not occur. Your use of the Sites and our Services is at your own risk. CSS urges you to take steps to keep your information safe by memorizing your password or keeping it in a safe place (separate from your account information), logging out of your account, and closing your Web browser. In addition, you should not provide your password to others. By registering for or using our Services, you are responsible for any use of our Services accomplished through the use of your password.

We cannot and do not ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to CSS and you do so at your own risk.

## Use of Your Information

We use your information, including your personal information, to provide our Services to you and for the following purposes:

  * To communicate with you, to respond to your inquiries, and for other customer services purposes;
  * To provide information that you have requested to receive from us;
  * To tailor the content and information that we may send or display to you, and to otherwise personalize your experiences while using our Services;
  * To improve our Services;
  * For research purposes;
  * For marketing and advertising purposes; for example, we may send you emails about new features of our Sites and our Applications as well as about our products and services, as well as products and services of third parties, that we believe would be of interest to you;
  * To better understand how users access and use our Services, both on an aggregated and individualized basis.

## Sharing Information

We may provide information, including your personal information (collectively, “information”), to non-affiliated and affiliated parties for a variety of purposes as described in this section and throughout this Privacy Policy.

_**Affiliates and Non-Affiliated Third Parties.**_ We may disclose your information to affiliates and non-affiliated companies when we believe their products or services may be of interest to you, so that they can contact you with offers. If you respond to an offer and provide information directly to another company, that information will be subject to their privacy policy, not this Privacy Policy. If you later decide that you do not want that third party to use your information, you will need to contact the third party directly. CSS is not responsible for the manner in which other businesses collect or use your personal information.

_**Joint Marketing Events/Partners.**_ We also may partner with third parties for joint marketing events. If you participate in such as an event, including a promotion as discussed below, we may share your information with the third party.

_**Third parties providing services on our behalf.**_ We may engage third parties to perform services in connection with the operation of our business. Examples of these services include: (a) distribution of marketing and promotional material; (b) website evaluation and analytics; (c) fulfilling magazine, newsletters or other subscriptions; (d) payment transactions for premium membership-related features; (e) data collection, storage, management, analysis and, where applicable, cleansing, and (f) any other services designed to assist us in maximizing our business potential. These third parties may have access to information about visitors to our Sites and our Applications, including personal information, for the purpose of performing their duties and functions.

  * Premium membership, payment processor. Tinypass is a service from Piano Software, Inc. This vendor provides us with the ability to offer premium memberships on [www.chickensoup.com](http://www.chickensoup.com/ "www.chickensoup.com"), and also handles payment transactions. If you become a premium member, you will be billed by Tinypass/Piano and you will be able to manage your billing information via Tinypass. Piano Software’s privacy policy: <https://piano.io/privacy-policy/>   
 
  * Email newsletters processor. Our email newsletters are processed and delivered by third-party email services. By subscribing to an email newsletter, you acknowledge and agree that your personal information (such as email address, name, country, and zip code) will be sent and processed according to their terms and privacy policies. 
    * For Chicken Soup for the Soul and A-Plus newsletters, we use the Postup platform, which is subject to the Postup privacy policy (<https://www.postup.com/privacy-policy/>).
    * For Popcornflix newsletters, we use the Mailchimp platform, which is subject to the Mailchimp privacy policy (<https://mailchimp.com/legal/privacy/>).
    * For Truli newsletters, we use the Constant Contact platform, which is subject to the Constant Contact privacy policy (<https://www.constantcontact.com/forward/privacy-center>).
  * Transactional email processor. Some of our Sites use Sendgrid, an email service provider, to be able to send transactional emails and other system notifications to us and our Sites’ users. Sendgrid’s privacy policy is at <https://sendgrid.com/policies/privacy/services-privacy-policy/>

_**Investigations and security**_. We may release information about you when legally required to do so, at the request of governmental authorities conducting an investigation, in response to a subpoena or other legal process, or to verify or enforce compliance with the policies governing our Sites, Applications, and applicable laws. We may also disclose such user information whenever we believe disclosure is necessary to protect the rights, property or safety of CSS, or any of our respective affiliates, subsidiaries, business partners, customers or others.

_**Aggregate Information.**_ We may disclose aggregated user statistics to third parties for a variety of purposes, including describing our services to prospective partners and other third parties, such as advertisers, and as otherwise described in this Privacy Policy. Examples of such non-personal information include the number of users who visited this Sites or Applications during a specific time period or purchased a specific product through this Sites or Applications. 

_**Promotions.**_ If you choose to enter a contest, sweepstakes or promotion offered by CSS, your information may be disclosed to third parties for purposes of posting your entry with attribution or otherwise as permitted in the official rules for the contest, sweepstakes or promotion in question, fulfilling your prize or including your name on a winners list, or as otherwise necessary for purposes of the contest, sweepstakes or promotion. We may also require you to consent to the use of your information, such as name, voice or likeness, in advertising, promotional and marketing materials, in which case the rules will so state. In addition, we may offer promotional content, including sweepstakes and promotions, sponsored by or co-branded with a third party, who may obtain the personal information that you submit. Please refer to the rules of the particular contest, sweepstakes or promotion for additional information. All promotional information offered by CSS will come with instructions on how to opt-out from receiving further information in the future.

_**Surveys.**_ CSS may from time to time conduct voluntary surveys of visitors to the Sites to obtain aggregate demographic information about them. Such information may be compiled and shared in the aggregate with advertisers and other third parties.

_**Business Transfers/Bankruptcy.**_ If we are acquired by or merged with another company, if substantially all of our assets are transferred to another company, or as part of a bankruptcy proceeding, we may transfer the information we have collected from you to the acquiring company.

## How Long We Will Hold Information

We will hold information about you on our systems for as long as is necessary for the relevant service, or as long as is set out in any relevant contract you hold with CSS, subject to any applicable laws and/or regulations. In the case that you wish to cancel your registration as a member of any of our Sites, once an account is deleted, we will not use the information about you other than for administrative purposes. Nonetheless, it stays on the system for a period of one year for administration purposes before being deleted. 

Where you contribute to the Sites, we will generally only keep your content for as long as is reasonably required for the purpose(s) for which it was submitted. See User Generated Content below.

## User Generated Content

Certain portions of our Services permit users to post content in contexts that do not have a restricted audience, including, for example, profile pages, discussion forum messages, blogs, commenting on an article, posting a picture, etc. Any information that you post using these features to our Services may be viewable by other visitors to our Services. We are not responsible for the privacy of your submissions, or for the accuracy of any information contained in those submissions. Any information that you disclose becomes public information. We cannot prevent such information from being used in a manner that may violate this Policy, the law or your personal privacy.

If you post or send offensive, inappropriate or objectionable content anywhere on or to the Sites, or otherwise engage in any disruptive behavior on the Sites, we may use the personal information we hold about you to stop such behavior. Where we reasonably believe that you are or may be in breach of any applicable laws (for example, but without limitation, content you have posted may be defamatory), we may use the personal information we hold to inform relevant third parties such as your employer, school email/Internet provider, or law enforcement agencies about the content and your behavior.

## Advertising

We use third parties such as network advertisers to serve advertisements on our Sites and email newsletters. Network advertisers are third parties that display advertisements based on your visits to our Site and other websites you have visited. This enables us and these third parties to target advertisements to you for products and services in which you might be interested. Third party ad network providers, advertisers, sponsors and/or traffic measurement services may use cookies, JavaScript, web beacons (including clear GIFs), Flash LSOs and other technologies to measure the effectiveness of their ads and to personalize advertising content to you. These third party cookies and other technologies are governed by each third party’s specific privacy policy, not this one. We may provide these third-party advertisers with information about your usage of our Sites and our Services on an aggregated basis.

Our third-party advertising vendors include Google, LiveIntent, PowerInbox, and others.

To opt out of personalized advertising from Google, visit the Google Ad settings page at <https://www.google.com/settings/ads>.

LiveIntent’s privacy policy: <https://liveintent.com/services-privacy-policy/>

PowerInbox’s privacy policy: <https://powerinbox.com/privacy-policy/>

**You may opt-out of third-party ad networks.** The website <http://www.networkadvertising.org/optout_nonppii.asp> provides information regarding this practice by Network Advertising Initiative (“NAI”) members, and your choices regarding having this information used by these companies, including how to “opt-out” of third-party ad networks operated by NAI members. You also may contact the Digital Advertising Alliance at <http://www.aboutads.info/choices/> for information about opting out of targeted advertising and your choices regarding having information used by About Ads member companies, including how to “opt-out” of third-party ad networks operated by About Ads members. Opting out of one or more NAI members or DAI members (many of which will be the same) only means that those members no longer will deliver targeted content or ads to you, but it does not mean you will no longer receive any targeted content or ads on our Sites or other websites. You may continue to receive advertisements, for example, based on the particular website that you are viewing. Also, if your browsers are configured to reject cookies when you visit this opt-out page, or you subsequently erase your cookies, use a different computer or change web browsers, your NAI or DAI opt-out may no longer, be effective. Additional information is available on NAI’s and DAI’s websites accessible by the above links.

## Our Commitment to Children’s Privacy

Protecting the privacy of children is important to us. We do not collect or maintain information from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our Services is structured to attract anyone under 13. If you are under the age of 13, you are not permitted to use our Services. If you are aware of anyone under the age of 13 using our Sites, please notify us. Upon confirmation, we will terminate any account that user may have, and we will eliminate any personal information we may have obtained from that user. This may involve us having to access and verify your age and other relevant details.

## Personal Information Review and Revision Policies

  * If you are a registered user or premium member of [www.chickensoup.com](http://www.chickensoup.com/ "www.chickensoup.com"), you may view and update your profile information by logging in and visiting your account settings page. To manage your premium membership or billing information, you can make changes by logging into your Tinypass account. For more information, [see our FAQ](https://www.chickensoup.com/about/faq).  
 
  * If you would like to review or update your personal information for email newsletters, send an email to [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#d0a0a2b9a6b1b3a9a1a5b5a2b9b5a390b3b8b9b3bbb5bea3bfa5a0b6bfa2a4b8b5a3bfa5bcfeb3bfbd) with “Newsletter – personal info request” in the subject line, and include your email address and the names of the newsletters you subscribe to (e.g. A-Plus, Chicken Soup for the Soul lists, Popcornflix), and your updated information.  
 
  * If you are a contributor to a Chicken Soup for the Soul book and would like to review or update your personal information, send an email to [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#93e4f6f1fef2e0e7f6e1d3f0fbfaf0f8f6fde0fce6e3f5fce1e7fbf6e0fce6ffbdf0fcfe) with “Contributor – personal info request” in the subject line, and include your name, email address, and a description of your request. If you need to change your contact information, please be sure to provide the old information as well as the new info, so we can find you.  
 
  * If you would like to review or update your personal information for any other of our Sites or Applications, send an email to [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#78080a110e191b01090d1d0a111d0b381b10111b131d160b170d081e170a0c101d0b170d14561b1715) with “Personal info request” in the subject line, and include your email address and the URLs and names of the sites, along with a description of your request.

## Unsubscribe and Data Removal Policies

  * If you no longer wish to receive email newsletters or promotional emails from us, please follow the unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of your newsletter email message. 

Please also note that if you opt-out of receiving promotional emails from us, we may continue to contact you with via email with service related communications.

  * You may also email us directly at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#4333312a3522203a323626312a263003202b2a2028262d302c3633252c31372b26302c362f6d202c2e) to unsubscribe from our email newsletters, or to delete your personal information from our email newsletter databases. Include the email address where you receive our newsletters and if possible, please forward a full copy of your email newsletter with your request.  
 
  * If you are a registered user of one or more of our Sites and would like to delete your account or remove your personal information such as name and email address,  
contact us at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#d8a8aab1aeb9bba1a9adbdaab1bdab98bbb0b1bbb3bdb6abb7ada8beb7aaacb0bdabb7adb4f6bbb7b5). In your request, include your name, username, email address associated with your account, and the URL for each site where you would like your information to be removed. 

Please note: We may ask for additional information in order for us to respond to your request efficiently. To protect your privacy, we may ask you to verify your identity before making changes to your personal information. [See here for further details](https://www.chickensoup.com/about/faq).

## Your California Privacy Rights

A California privacy law that went into effect on January 1, 2005, the "Shine the Light" law, allows California residents to obtain a list of third parties to whom a business has disclosed information if it shares such information with third parties for their direct marketing purposes. However, if a business adopts and discloses in its privacy policy a policy of not disclosing customers’ information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes unless the customer first affirmatively agrees to the disclosure, the business may comply with the law by notifying the customer of his or her right to prevent disclosure of information and by providing a cost-free means to exercise that right.

As stated earlier in this Privacy Policy, information submitted at the time of registration or submission may be used for marketing and promotional purposes only with the user’s permission. Whenever a user agrees to allow us to collect information, we provide the user with an option to prevent such information from being shared for marketing and promotional purposes with third parties. Furthermore, you may exercise this cost-free option at any time by emailing us at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#c4b4b6adb2a5a7bdb5b1a1b6ada1b784a7acada7afa1aab7abb1b4a2abb6b0aca1b7abb1a8eaa7aba9) with the subject line “Marketing Opt Out” and including your name, email address, and (if applicable) the URLs and usernames of your accounts on our Sites.

Because the Sites have a comprehensive Privacy Policy and provide you with details on how you may opt-in or opt-out of the use of your information by third parties for direct marketing purposes, we are not required to provide you with the third party list.

## Other Sites and Services

CSS may contain links to, or advertisements about, non-CSS websites. Other sites may also reference, advertise or link to the Site. CSS does not endorse or sponsor other websites, is not responsible for their privacy practices or content, expressly disclaims any statements or assertions made on such websites, and denies all liability associated with your use of, and the content on, such other websites and advertisements. Please be advised that the practices described in this Privacy Policy do not apply to information gathered through other websites. We encourage you to be aware of when you leave our Services and to read the privacy policies of each website that you use.

## Consent to Processing in the United States

Our Services are operated in the United States. By providing any information to CSS, all users, including, without limitation, users in the member states of the European Union, Canada or elsewhere outside of the United States, fully understand and consent to this Privacy Policy. That means by using our Sites, participating in any of our Services and/or providing us with your information, you consent to the collection, transfer, storage, use and processing of your personal information to and in the United States in accordance with this Privacy Policy. If you are visiting from the European Union or other regions with laws governing data collection and use that may differ from United States law, please note that you are transferring your personal information to the United States. The laws of some countries may not provide the same levels of protection of personal information as your home country, particularly if you are resident in the European Union. We will take reasonable steps to ensure that information about you is treated securely in accordance with this Privacy Policy, and that all information you provide to us is stored on our secure servers or those of our service providers. 

YOU ACKNOWLEDGE THAT THE LAWS OF THE UNITED STATES TREAT YOUR INFORMATION IN A MANNER THAT MAY BE SUBSTANTIALLY DIFFERENT FROM, AND LESS PROTECTIVE THAN, THE TREATMENT REQUIRED UNDER THE LAWS OF OTHER COUNTRIES AND JURISDICTIONS. IF YOU DO NOT WANT YOUR INFORMATION TRANSFERRED TO THE UNITED STATES, YOU SHOULD NOT SHARE YOUR INFORMATION WITH US, OR MAKE USE OF THESE WEBSITES.

TO THE EXTENT ALLOWED BY THE LAW OF THE COUNTRY IN WHICH YOU ARE LOCATED, YOU EXPRESSLY WAIVE ANY RIGHT YOU MAY HAVE TO REQUIRE US TO TREAT YOUR INFORMATION IN ACCORDANCE WITH THE LAWS OF ANY COUNTRY OR JURISIDICTION OTHER THAN THE UNITED STATES. HOWEVER, THE FOREGOING WAIVER MAY NOT BE LEGALLY BINDING IN SOME COUNTRIES, SUCH AS THE MEMBER STATES OF THE EUROPEAN UNION. TO THE EXTENT IT IS NOT LEGALLY BINDING IN THE COUNTRY IN WHICH YOU ARE LOCATED, THIS FOREGOING WAIVER DOES NOT APPLY TO YOU.

## Revisions to Privacy Policy

We reserve the right, in our sole discretion, to modify, update, add to, discontinue, remove or otherwise change any portion of this Privacy Policy, in whole or in part, at any time. When we amend this Privacy Policy, we will revise the “last updated” date located at the top of this Privacy Policy. For changes to this Privacy Policy that we consider to be material, we will place a notice on the CSS websites located at [www.chickensoup.com](https://www.chickensoup.com/), [chickensouppets.com](https://chickensouppets.com/), [aplus.com](https://aplus.com/), [www.popcornflix.com](https://www.popcornflix.com/), [cssentertainment.com](https://cssentertainment.com/), [www.screenmedia.net](http://www.screenmedia.net/ "www.screenmedia.net"), and [www.truli.com](http://www.truli.com/ "www.truli.com") by revising the link to read as “Updated Privacy Policy” for a reasonable amount of time. By providing information to us or using our Services in any way after this Privacy Policy has been revised, you consent and agree to the revised Privacy Policy. The most current version of this Privacy Policy will be available on the Sites and will supersede all previous versions of this Privacy Policy.

## Choice of Law

This Privacy Policy, including all revisions and amendments thereto, and any disputes arising from or relating to this Privacy Policy or your use of our Services, is governed by the laws of the State of Connecticut without regard to any conflict or choice of law principles that would require application of the laws of another jurisdiction.

**Legal disclaimer**

We are not responsible nor will be liable to you in any way for events beyond our direct control. Because of the complex and constantly changing nature of our technology and business, we cannot guarantee nor do we represent that our performance will be error free, and to the maximum extent permitted by law we will not be liable for any direct, indirect, incidental, consequential or punitive damages or other loss suffered by you and relating to the use or release of your information.

## Questions about our Privacy Policy

If you have any further questions or concerns about CSS’s privacy policies and use of information, please send them to [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#d8a8aab1aeb9bba1a9adbdaab1bdab98bbb0b1bbb3bdb6abb7ada8beb7aaacb0bdabb7adb4f6bbb7b5) and include the name and/or website addresses of the Sites or Applications in your message, so we may better assist you with your inquiry.

You can also write us at:

Attn: Data Privacy Officer  
Chicken Soup for the Soul  
P.O. Box 700  
Cos Cob, CT 06807-0700  
United States.

All rights reserved.
